One hundred thirty-five students, four teachers, one giant classroom: This is what 9th grade looks like at Westwood High School, in Mesa, Arizona’s largest school system.
一百三十五名学生，四位教师，一间巨大的教室：在亚利桑那州规模最大的梅萨学区，韦斯特伍德高中的九年级就是这个样子。
There, an innovative teaching model has taken hold, and is spreading to other schools in the district and beyond.
在那里，一种创新教学模式已经站稳脚跟，并正在向学区内的其他学校乃至学区以外推广。
Five years ago, faced with high teacher turnover and declining student enrollment, Westwood’s leaders decided to try something different.
五年前，面对教师流动率高、学生入学人数下降的局面，韦斯特伍德高中的领导层决定尝试一些不同的做法。
Working with professors at Arizona State University’s teachers college, they piloted a classroom model known as team teaching, which allows teachers to dissolve the walls that separate their classes across physical or grade divides.
他们与亚利桑那州立大学师范学院的教授合作，试行了一种名为“团队教学”的课堂模式，这种模式让教师能够打破隔开各自班级的墙，不论班级之间隔着的是物理空间还是年级界限。
The teachers share large groups of students—sometimes 100 or more—and rotate between group instruction, one-on-one interventions, small study groups, and whatever the teachers as a team agree is a priority that day.
这些教师共同负责一大批学生——有时多达100名甚至更多——并在集体授课、一对一辅导、小型学习小组以及教师团队一致认为当天需要优先处理的事情之间轮换。
What looks at times like chaos is in fact a carefully orchestrated plan: Each morning, the Westwood teams meet to hammer out a personalized program for every student the team will focus on that day.
有时看起来一片混乱的场面，其实是一项精心安排的计划：每天早上，韦斯特伍德高中的各个教师团队都会开会，为团队当天要重点关注的每一名学生敲定一套个性化方案。
By giving teachers more opportunity to collaborate, Mesa’s administrators hoped to fill staffing gaps and boost teacher morale and retention.
梅萨学区的管理人员希望通过给教师更多合作机会，来填补人员缺口，提振教师士气，提高教师留任率。
Initial research suggests the gamble could pay off.
初步研究表明，这次冒险可能会有回报。
“Teachers are doing fantastic things, but it’s very rare a teacher walks into another room to see what’s happening,” said Andi Fourlis, superintendent of Mesa Public Schools.
“老师们在做着很了不起的事，但很少有老师会走进另一间教室，去看看那里的情况。”梅萨公立学校学区总监安迪·福尔利斯说。
“Our profession is so slow to advance because we are working in isolation.”
“我们这个行业之所以进步如此缓慢，是因为我们都在单打独斗。”
Of course, overhauling teaching approaches can’t fix all the frustrations teachers have, such as low pay, but early results from Mesa show team teaching may be helping to reverse low morale.
当然，彻底改革教学方法并不能解决教师所有的烦恼，比如工资低，但梅萨学区的初步结果显示，团队教学可能正在帮助扭转士气低落的局面。
In a survey of hundreds of the district’s teachers, researchers found those who worked on teams reported greater job satisfaction, more frequent collaborations with colleagues, and more positive interactions with students.
在一项针对该学区数百名教师的调查中，研究人员发现，参与团队的教师表示，他们的工作满意度更高，与同事合作更频繁，与学生的互动也更积极。
Another benefit of teams, teachers say, is that they can help each other improve their instruction.
教师们说，团队的另一个好处是，他们可以互相帮助，改进教学。
During one planning session, English teacher Jeff Hall shared a performance appraisal with a science teacher: Her recent lecture on something she called “the central dogma of biology” had bewildered him and their other teammates.
在一次备课会上，英语教师杰夫·霍尔向一位科学教师说出了对她教学表现的评价：她最近讲了一堂课，内容是她所说的“生物学中心法则”，这堂课让他和团队里的其他同事都一头雾水。
“If the science is too confusing for me, can you imagine the frustration you feel as kids?” Hall said.
“如果这些科学内容对我来说太难懂了，那你能想象身为孩子会有多沮丧吗？”霍尔说。
But the science teacher, he said, wouldn’t have known about the confusion on her own.
但他说，那位科学教师单靠自己，本来是不会知道有这种困惑的。
The model is not for everyone.
这种模式并非人人适用。
Some teachers approached about volunteering for a team have said they prefer to work alone.
一些教师在被问及是否愿意主动报名加入团队时表示，他们更喜欢独自工作。
Team teaching can also be a scheduling nightmare, especially at schools like Westwood where only some staff work in teams.
团队教学也可能让排课变成一场噩梦，尤其是在像韦斯特伍德高中这样只有部分教职员工以团队形式工作的学校。
There are also thorny questions like how to evaluate four teachers on the performance of 135 students.
此外还有一些棘手的问题，比如如何根据135名学生的表现来评价四位教师。
But for the time being, it seems to be working.
但就目前而言，这种模式似乎正在奏效。